<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <author>
    <name>mose</name>
  </author>
  <id>http://greenruby.org/feed.rss</id>
  <title>Green Ruby</title>
  <updated>2014-02-02T16:00:23+08:00</updated>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-051.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-051.html"/>
    <summary>Next week it's chinese new year here in Taipei. During that holiday, I plan to secretly work on a dynamic version of Green Ruby website where we can filter and search links by tags or title. There may also be some redesign involved. But shht, it's secret and not even sure it will pan out.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #051</title>
    <updated>2014-01-26T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2014-01-26T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-050.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-050.html"/>
    <summary>In 2 weeks there is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://geekli.st/hackathon/52c49d837689332d5f000019&quot;&gt;5th geeklist world-wide hackacthon&lt;/a&gt;, maybe you are interested in joining and/or suggesting projects, that can be fun.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #050</title>
    <updated>2014-01-19T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2014-01-19T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-049.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-049.html"/>
    <summary>As we are approaching the first year of publication of this newsletter, it's time to think about the birthday party. It should happen in Taipei, Taiwan, after chinese new year. If you want to join, or know a good place where we could gather, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:news@greenruby.org&quot;&gt;drop me a mail&lt;/a&gt;.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #049</title>
    <updated>2014-01-12T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2014-01-12T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-048.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-048.html"/>
    <summary>Okay there is a new year digit, let's get back to work now. And btw feel free to visit us on #greenruby on freenode.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #048</title>
    <updated>2014-01-05T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2014-01-05T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-047.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-047.html"/>
    <summary>This week podcasters are in holidays, but ruby is not, here is v2.1 coming out. And various other notable releases visibly wanted to get out before 2014. All good for us :) See you next year!</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #047</title>
    <updated>2013-12-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-12-29T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-046.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-046.html"/>
    <summary>Now there are 100 subscribers to this newsletter, from 28 different countries. Nothing compared to the other publishers out there, but I have no time and interest in promotion. After all this weekly mail was just intended to be sent to a dozen of friends. And it went on like a personal habit, forcing me to keep in touch with the flow. Anyways, if I don't know you and if you like it, I'm happy enough. (and xenor is too). Happy hollidays if you get any!</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #046</title>
    <updated>2013-12-22T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-12-22T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-045.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-045.html"/>
    <summary>The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's just twice as big as it needs to be.&lt;br&gt; (just an unknown geek quote).</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #045</title>
    <updated>2013-12-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-12-15T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-044.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-044.html"/>
    <summary>This week on tuesday we had various security alerts on rails, all versions. It's a good time to upgrade or to think about how to get rid of your rails 2 remaining apps. I know there are still a lot out there.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #044</title>
    <updated>2013-12-08T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-12-08T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-043.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-043.html"/>
    <summary>It's harder and harder to keep this letter to a decent size, there are so many things happening each week. And I confess I like to keep the topics a bit wider than just ruby or webdev. My bad. But I wonder, what you readers think about it ? Feels free to just hit reply on this mail and share your thoughts.</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #043</title>
    <updated>2013-12-01T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-12-01T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>http://greenruby.org/grn-042.html</id>
    <link href="http://greenruby.org/grn-042.html"/>
    <summary>42. Here we are. This memetic number marks an accomplishement in itself. Well, be sure to upgrade your ruby for the occasion, and if you still run 1.8, hum, you are screwed (unless you are on heroku, they patched their version).</summary>
    <title>Green Ruby News #042</title>
    <updated>2013-11-24T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2013-11-24T00:00:00+08:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <dc:date>2014-02-02T16:00:23+08:00</dc:date>
</feed>
